Insurance Corporation Limited,
like the head has 64 persons stake and the rest,
Vijay Partner ICC has 64 percent stake in the head
and the rest are children, the stake is
with Vijay Partners, Fairfax
Finance, Fair Facts Finance exited in
2019 by selling two remaining five persons stake in the
company for
2600 crores, what did Fair Facts Finance do, they exited
in 2019 and sold 5% of their stake
which was worth 2600 crores, so
friends, now we have known about the company,
next we know the fundamentals of the company, the
current price of its stock is also
running, it is running at
1234, the maximum till now has gone up to
1369, the maximum till now has gone up to
149, the market cap of this stock is
60000 632 crores, so the ratio of
this stock is 35.1  The stock's net worth is 21.2%, the
sales growth in 3 years
is 15.8%, the
book value of this stock is 230, the ROI is 17.6
%, the APPS is
35.2%, the sales growth is 11.5%,
ROI in 7 years has been 23.4%, which means it is providing this dividend to its investors,
provide it, the face value of 0.73% of this stock
is 10, the sales growth in 5 years has been 20.9%, the
ROI in 7 years has been
18.4%, the
overall fundamentals of the stock are
strong, next we
know the pros and cons of the stock, what are the
merits and demerits of the stock, first of all we
know the ROI, the company has reduced debt, the company is
almost debt free company  The
company has reduced its dividend by maintaining a healthy dividend
and payout of
28.8%. The company has maintained its healthy dividend
payout of 28.8%.
Next, we know the company's earnings include
earnings and other income of Rs. 995
crore. Including earning, other income
is ₹995 crore.
After that, the promoter holding has
decreased over the last three years - 7.8%. There has been a
slight decrease in promoter holding.
Friends, who else were you? Next, we
know the share holding pattern of the company,
which is a very important factor. So,
friends, in their share holding pattern, the
promoter holding in June 2020 was
51.89%, which is now
48.03% in March 2023. The holding of FI
in June 2020 was 26.61%, which is in March 2023.  It is
22.85%
Didi's holding which was in June 2020
was 14.03 which is now
17.23% in March 2023 Public involvement in June
2017.47% because in March 2023
public involvement is 11.73%
Overall share holding pattern is also good
You can pick this stock in your portfolio for
further investment purpose
This was my stock analysis friends you
can pick it according to your own Thank
you So watching on Match
[Music]